Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
Gordon Leo McDonough papers
1920-1965
0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
105.0 linear ft. 105 boxes
Papers of Gordon Leo McDonough, member of the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors and the United States Congress.
McDonough, Gordon Leo, 1895-1968
Access
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required for access.
Scope and Content
Papers of Gordon Leo McDonough, member of the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors and the United States Congress.
Biography
McDonough, Gordon Leo - born in Buffalo, Erie County, New York, January 2, 1895; moved with his parents to Emporium, Cameron County, Pennsylvania in 1898; attended the public schools; was graduated from the high school at Emporium; engaged as an industrial chemist at Emporium 1915-1918; moved to Los Angeles, California and resumed his former occupation 1918-1933; member of the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors 1933-1944, serving as chairman for one year; elected as a Republican to the Seventy-ninth and to the eight succeeding Congresses (January 3, 1945-January 3, 1963); unsuccessful candidate for reelection in 1962 to the Eighty-eighth Congress; died in Bethesda, Maryland, June 25, 1968; interment in Holy Cross Mausoleum, Los Angeles, California
Arrangement
Listing of headings used arranged alphabetically by HEADING with time period, box contents arrangement, related correspondance, related bill(s), subject(s), committee(s), box number(s), color dot marking, number of boxes. The collection consists of 16 subsections under chronological order. Index of sub-headingswere made of Bills, Cases, Legislation, Miscellaneous, Roll Call Subjects.
Contents of related bill(s), subject(s), committee(s) were extracted from correspondence
Also belonging to the collection is a filing cabinet containing 4 drawers, numbered 1 thr. 4. Each drawer contains a [UNK].
Los Angeles County (Calif.). Board of Supervisors. -- Archives; McDonough, Gordon Leo, 1895-1968 -- Archives; United States. Congress. -- Archives; Los Angeles County (Calif.)--Politics and government--Archival resources; Politicians--California--Archival resources; United States--Politics and government--20th century--Archival resources
- AIRCRAFT/NAVY APPLICANTS, 1954-1964 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Arr. alphabetically by name, year(s) of corr., related subject(s)
- BILLS RELIF BILLS, 1945-1964 (Box 2-14)
  Arr. by bill nr., subject(s), year(s) of corr., related bill(s)
- CASES, 1945-1963 (Box 16-35)
  Arr. alphabetically by subject, year(s) of corr, related bill(s)
- COMMITTEES, 1945-1950 (Box 36-38)
  Arr. by committee, year(s) of corr., related bill(s) subject(s)
- GENERAL CORRESPONDANCE, 1945-1956 (Box 39-42)
  Arr. alphabetically by heading, year(s) of corr., relatedbill(s), subject(s)
- LEGISLATION, 1945-1962 (Box 43-55)
  Arr. alphabetically by subject, year(s) of corr., related bill(s)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDANCE, 1961/62 (Box 56-57)
  Arr. alphabetically by topic, year(s) of corr., related bill(s) subject(s)
- LEGISLATIVE/POLITICAL SUBJECTS, 1945-1961 (Box Box 58)
  Arr. alphabetically by subject C through S, related corr.
- MILITARY ACADEMY WEST POINT MERCHANT MARINE, 1954-1963 (Box Box 59)
  Arr. aphabetically by heading, year(s) of corr., related subject(s)
- OFFICE, 1945-1962 (Box Box 60)
  Arr. folder heading, year(s) of corr., related bill(s) subject(s)
- PRESS RELEASE REMARKS STATEMENTS, 1943-1963 (Box Box 61)
  Arr. alphabetically by heading
- ROLL CALL RECORD (Box Box 62)
  Arr. alphabeticaaly by heading, corr. related bill(s), subject(s)
- SUBJECT GENERAL (Box 63-67)
  Arr. alphabetically by heading, year(s) of corr., related bill(s), organisation(s), subject(s)
- PERSONAL PERSONAL POLITICAL SPECIAL POLITICAL corr. (Box 68-73)
  Correspondence in boxes with label P PP SP
  Arr. by heading, year(s) or parts of year chronological
- CORRESPONDANCE OUT-GOING (yellow copies of letters) (Box 74-89)
  by year(s) with separators A-Z
- MISCELLANEOUS, 1920-1962 (Box 90-102)
- WASHINGTON REPORTS (Box Box W R 15)
- FAVOR** file (Box 103-105)
  see note preceding lists
- File AIRFORCE NAVY applicants, 1954-1964
  Arr. aphabetically by applicant/subject
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY applicants (out of District, 1955-62) (Box 1)
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY information (nomination forms, appointments), 1954-60
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY Results, 1956-57
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY nomination papers data for, 1962, '61
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY results entering class (prior academic requirements, report of board of visitors), 1961, '62
  - AIRFORCE ACADEMY APPLICATIONS
  - Ash 2nd alternate, 1962
  - Beeson, 1959, '60 '61
  - Bennett, 1957 '56
  - Bliss, 1954 '55
  - Bonynge, 1960
  - Borokoff 3rd alternate, 1958
  - Bowers, 1962
  - Brown 8th alternate, 1959 '60
  - Bryan 1st alternate, 1962
  - Colby, 1960
  - Duke, 1957
  - Fedrick, 1961 '60
  - Feinblatt, 1961 '60
  - Garcia, 1961 '60
  - Garard, 1961
  - Hazzlet (out of District), 1958
  - Hillman not nominated, 1955 '56
  - Huber 4th alternate, 1961 '62
  - Ito, 1962 '63
  - Johnson, 1961 '60
  - Kellar, 1963 '62
  - Ledour, 1957 '56
  - Mack, 1958 '57
  - Mackinney, 1958
  - Maddox, 1957
  - Martin, 1961 '60
  - Matsui, 1962 '61
  - Mikulay 3rd alternate, 1962 '61
  - Mischbueaux 4th alternate, 1960 '59
  - Mulvany, 1963 '62
  - Oso[UNK] 7th alternate, physically disqualified, 1960
  - Paine 1st alternate, 1961 '62
  - Parker, 1958 '57
  - Pelaes 5th alternate, 1962
  - Robinson, 1963
  - Ryan 3rd alternate, 1960 '57 '58 '59
  - ANDERSEN Naval Academy principal, 1963 '61
  - Bartling, Herbert Annapolis examination reports, 1945 '46
  - Baus Naval Academy, 1956 '55
  - Beron-Graduate Naval Academy 1st alternate, 1958 '53 '54 '57
  - Buether Naval Academy 4th alternate, 1958
  - Bull, Ingall Academy, 1945
  - Burgard J Naval Academy 3rd alternate admitted June, 1954 '54
  - Burgard R Naval Academy admitted, 1961 '56 '57 '57
  - Conley D Naval Academy graduates, 1959 1963
  - Fahey J P Annapolis graduates, 1954 '49 '50
  - Fahey R L Annapolis applicant Principal, 1954 '53
  - Ford S. Navy Academy Promised principal, 1963 '62
  - Galbraith P Navy Academy Principal, 1961 '60
  - Goldsmith Navy Academy, 1957 '56
  - Griesse, R Navy Academy, 1956 '55 '54
  - Hart, R L Annapolis graduate, 1952 '46 '47
  - Herrell J Navy Academy 1st alternate to Ford, 1963 '62
  - Jacobs Navy Academy graduates 2nd alternate - admitted, 1958 '53 '54
  - Julian, Thomas Annapolis graduated, 1952 '53
  - Kamp, James Annapolis graduated, 1956 '52
  - Kay Navy academy 1st alternate to Galbraith - disqualified, 1961 '59 '60
  - Kenney Disqualified physically, 1957
  - NAVAL ACADEMY (ANNAPOLIS) Congressional examinations for designation of candidates for appointments, lists of applications received, officer qualifications practise boooklets, methods of qualification mentally for admission, chart., 1945
  - NAVAL ACADEMY PAPERS Annual Congressional examinations, nominations forms, mental examination for midshipmen, midshipmen nominations., 1946-47
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Applicants Annapolis applicants, candidates class, 1045-48 1948
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Appointment forms, 1963
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Examinations results midshipmen, 1960
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Information lists admitted candidates, 1960 '59
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Requests out of district, 1951 '52
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Results entering class, 1961
  - NAVAL ACADEMY Results, 1953
  - NAVAL ACADEMY statement to Board of Visitors, 1962 '61
  - Lemming Annapolis applicant, 1954 '53
  - Libry Military Academy 3rd alternate, 1957 '58
  - Lutz Annapolis graduate, 1957 '53
  - Mahan Nacal Academy principal, 1960 '62
  - Matthews Naval Academy 3rd alternate to Neary, 1958 '57
  - Maxfield Naval Academy graduate formerly Airforce acdemy, 1960 '55 '56
  - Missler Annapolis graduates, 1956 '52
  - Mizrahi Annapolis applicant no grades forms received, 1954 '53
  - Moore Navy Academy graduate, 1960 '55 '56 '58
  - Neary Navy Academy principal, 1958 '57 '59
  - O'Connor Navy Academy principal, 1960 '59 '60
  - Parode Annapolis graduates, 1950 '46 '45
  - Quinn Annapolis applicant, 1952
  - Radvanczy Navy Academy 3rd alternate to Greaith, 1961
  - Robenson Annapolis 2nd alternate -admitted by Board, 1961 '60 '59
  - Robenson Annapolis 1st alternate to Missler, 1951 '52
  - Rogers Naval Academy principal-graduated, 1959 1963
  - Schecter Candidate Annapolis Applicant, 1955
  - Schertle Military Academy, 1958 '57
  - Sheerley Annapolis graduates, 1953 '49
  - Sprague Naval Academy 1st alternate to Neary, 1958
  - Stegam Naval Academy US Civil Service Comm. examination sheets, 1945
  - Stevenson Naval Academy 2nd aterate to Conley, 1959
  - Sthol Naval Academy graduated Public Law 586, 1959 '63
  - Stoddard Annapolis graduate, 1957 '51 '52 '53
  - Stucker Naval Academy 1st alternate to Conlry, 1959
  - Sutch Naval Academy withdrawn, 1959 '58
  - Surn Military academy out of district, 1958
  - Thomasset Naval Academy 4th alternate to Galbraith, 1961 '60
  - Towne Naval Academy for consideration, 1956 '54 '55
  - Welsh Annapolis graduated, 1952 '48
  - Wu Naval Academy Graduates, 1959 '55
  - Nelson Naval Academy, 1960 '59 '58
- File of BILLS/RELIEF bills sponsored/introduced by Sen. McDonough
  contains Boxes 2 thr. 14
  1955 - '64 in boxes labelled BILLS
  Arr. by bill in folders
  - BILLS introduced by Sen McDounough, 1943-1947
    78/79 Congress
    Arranged by Bill nr.
    - Amend Soldiers Sailors Civil Relief Act as amended 78 Congr. COSTELLO BILL, 1943; H R 1823 (Box Box 2)
    - Social Security Amendment 78 Congr. H R 3575, 1946; 473
    - Extension Insurance FHA loans to Vets. H R 127 1176 2824 3749 4082 4256, 1946, '45 '47; 474
    - Vivisection in District of Columbia H R 33 (Enveloppe), 1945; 491
    - Vivisection in District of Columbia LEMKE BILL (Enveloppe), 1945
    - Vivisection in District of Columbia (Enveloppe), 1945
    - Jr.Military Academy 78 Congr. HR 2250 2608 4990, 1943, '41; 829
    - Costello Bill 78 Congr. H R 2669 6791 (amend fair labor standards act), 1943; 835
    - Highest was rank to retired officers Costello BILL H R 7659, 1943, '42; 833
    - West Coast Navy Academy, 77 Congr. S 839 76 Congr., 1945; 1371
    - Merchant Marine Hospital at L A, 1945; 1373
    - Surplus Property 78 Congr. HR 2016 2017 Public Law 225 457, 1945; 2016
    - Granting certain benefits priorites in connection with the acq. of surplus property H R 2017 2016 2649, 1945; 2016
    - To amend mustering-out act of granting to Vets certan benefits priorities in connection withsurplus property H R 2016, 1944 1945; 2017
    - Extend life of national service life insurance to 10 years, 1945; 2441
    - Reduce rate of interest on government insurance loans to 3 79 Congr., 1945; 2448
    - Advancement on retired list of certain USA AUS officres 78 Congr. COSTEELO BILL H R 260 Public Law 464 597, 1943, '44; 2702
    - McDounough Bill Amend G I Bill of Rights Public Law 346 (service readjustment act of, 1945 1944; 2824
    - Strike out provision in Servicemans' Readjustement Act of, 1944, '45; 2824
    - Strike out provision in Servicemans' Readjustement Act of S 1248 1285, 1945; 2827
    - Release of persons from active military service etc. 1297, 1945; 2827
    - Retirement of certain regular army officers previously physically retired, 78 Congr., 1943, '44; 3871
    - RELIEF BILLS
    - Sadie Ford (COSTEELO BILLS listing 74 thr. 78 Congress, 1943, '44; H R 926
    - Wilmot Fran E COSTELLO BILL), 1944, '43; 1269
    - Wissmann, Susan A Private Law 739 79 Congr., 1945, '46; 2287
    - Religious representation peace conference 79 Congr, 1945; H J RES 83
    - Title on oil lands 79 Congr., 1945; 217
    - Maps relating to reclaimed tide submerged lands
    - Against Truman Labor Bill, 1946; -
    - Congressman McDoungh Biils (arr. by subject in folder), 1945
    - Record of McDoungh Bills 79 Congr.(legisl records, dicharge petitions, 1945 1945
  - BILLS sponsored/ introduced by Sen McDonough, 1946/48
    Arranged by Bills in folios 1
    - Terminal leave in cash, 1947; 117 (Box Box 3)
    - Keeler H R 4075 Private Law 17, 1947; H R 765
    - Prohibit certain surplus property disposal 45 H R 2649, 1947, '; 119
    - Increase subsistance allownace G I educational job training P L 679 L L 346 H R 246 870, 1947; 960
    - World war I II combination Enblem, 1947; 1282
    - Discharge buttons (unauthorized wearing) H R 733, 1947; 1828
    - Place retired list officers World War I H R 4183, 1947, '46; 2031
    - Railroads, 1947, '46; 3227
    - Prevent deduction from veterans pay for hospitalization, 1945, '46; 3280
    - G I Bill of amendments rights H R 3938, 1945; 4082
    - Place on retired list officers Army World War I H R 4980, 1946; 4183
    - Data. Labor management relations Act Amendments pg. 1? 27 S 1613, 1947; 4193-94
    - Internal Revenue Amend. (Motion picture) 48 H R 4259 4866, 1947, '; 4846
    - Veterans Housing H R 4488 4581 S 1759, 1947; 4621
    - Advance grade of veterans, 1946; 4939
    - Costello (place on retired list officres Army World war I H R 2072, 4980
    - Fixing ranks of retired Army officers Vets H R 4939, 1946; 5226
    - Veterans compensation, pensions, retirement not reduced during hospital care, 1946; 5549
    - Equal Rights for D C, 1945, '56; 5629
    - Extension L A Post Office 1948 Public Law 785, 5750
    - R Huebscher, 1946; 5883
  - RELIEF BILLS same arrangement
    - KutkiwskyS S H R 3014, 1945, '46 '49; 766 (Box 3)
    - Keith H R 1170 1061 5339, 1949, '47 '48; 1057
    - Lass H R 5702 Private Law 116, 1949, '48; 1058
    - Grauss H R 767 2511 Private Law 94, 1949, '45 '49; 1062
    - Ruth Toohig, 1947; 1507
    - ?, 1947; 2061
    - ? H R 1142 Private Law 290, 1947, '48; 3225
    - Toporow Private Law 90, 1947; 3243
    - John A Watson, 1945, '46; 3741
    - Mrs Florence Mersman H R 5332 Pritare Law 343, 1945 '46; 3791
    - Frank E Wilmot Private Law 523, 1945; 4240
    - Gabrellierl H R 5224, 1945 '46; 4241
    - Seidler H R 4403 2287, 4920
    - Jefferson Davis H R 6254, 1948; 6254
    - Costillo Bill (relief Mrs Morsman), 1944; 125332
    - ? (Private Law 848), 1946; 135414
    - RECORD of Congressman Mc Donough 80th Congress 1st 2nd Session, 1947-48
    - RECORD of Congressman Mc Donough 83rd Congress 1st 2nd Session, 1953-54
    - RECORD of Congressman Mc Donough 85 Congress 1st 2nd Session, 1957-58
    - RECORD of Congressman Mc Donough 82 Congress 1st 2nd Session, 1951-52
  - BILLS introduced by Sen. McDonough, 1946- '59
    - Reduce interest rate on Government loans, 1947, '45; H R 118 (Box Box 4)
    - Amvets incorporation H R 120, H R 1888, H R 6781, 1946, '47; 120
    - Repeal Tax on transportation of property H R 205, H R 208 H R 1228, 1949; 205
    - Theatre Tax H R 206, H R 5038, 1949, '48; 206
    - Repeal Tax on certain telgraph tephone, radio cable facilites, 1949; 207
    - Repeal Tax on transportation of persons H R 1228, 1949; 208
    - Pensions to daughters of Vets War, 1812, 1847, '48; 586
    - Prohibit unauthorised wearing of discharge buttons H R 249 H R 733 H R 735 H R 1828, 1946, '47; 733
    - Advancement listof Persons Retired 30 years or more H R 332 H R 10955, 1149, Pbl.Law 381, 1957, '56; 1149
    - Valley Authority H R 341, 2487, 5384, 5804, 1957, '49; 1191
    - Increse in retirment benefits of certain Postal Employee's, 1957; 1197
    - Tax exemption for those who are 65 with income $ 3500 or less H R 11669, 1958; 1275
    - Amend Social Security Act, 1st $ 50 of income be disregared by State Agency H R 12312, 1958; 1276
    - Tax adjustment for certain Airpollution elimination H R 1174, 2417, 1954, '55; 1277
    - Amend Internal Revenue Code retaxartion of certain casuality losses H R 333, 9747, 1955 '56; 1283
    - Exempt certain Admissions from Excie Tax H R 325, 1182, 2288, 1953; 1284
    - $2400 Allownce for Income Tax Deductions on Pensions H R 336, 225, 5180, 5452, 1957 '54 '47 '47 '49; 1288
    - Weather Reports H R 5391, 1957, '58 '55; 1298
    - Permit Asiatics to citiznship (Naturalised) H R 199, 1623, 1951, '50; 1366
    - Vadasz Relief H R 9940, 1957 '56; 1578
    - To correct records in certain instances H R 1108, 4928, 1957; 33182
    - Define Combat Communism J Res 99, H R 5082, 1948 '47; 4581
    - Extension improvement of L A Postoffice facilities, 1948; 4845
    - House of Representatives Less than honourable discharge H R 8772, 4928
    - Tax Reduction forhome repair maintenance, 1957 '58; 5899
    - Extend subsurface rights to owner of surface rights on certain property, 1957; 6388
    - Olympic Games (Winter) H R 10729, 1958; 10713
    - Rights of Blinds to organise S 2411. H R 8609, 1958; 10179
    - Flood Control S 3688, 1958; 12439
    - Government Oil Contracts, 1958; 12440
    - Cabrillo Islands, 1958; 12985
    - Define Communism, 1947; J RES 99
    - Trade Exposition, 1958; H T RES 658
    - Prohibit Exportation of Sugar/ End sugar rationing H J Ra 146, 1947; H R 980
    - No deductions Veterans while hospitalized H R 322, 340, 1187, 4192, 4825, 776 Pybic Law 662, 1957 '47 '48 '49 '54; 1142
    - Tax Emption f. religious, educational charity organisations H R 326 1198 1587, 1953; 1278
    - Public Health Bill, 1948; 7017
  - BILLS introduced by McDonough, 1947-'58
    - Labor Civil Liberties, 1947, '48 '49; 203 (Box Box 5)
    - Repeal Cosmetic Tax Leather goods, 1950; 204
    - Repeal Tax Transportation of Property, 1950, '49; H R 205
    - Repeal Amusement Tax, 1950; 206
    - Repeal Communications Tax, 1949, '50; 207
    - Telegram Tax, 1949; 207
    - Repeal Tax Transportation of persons, 1950; 208
    - Equalize Labor Management (H R 4193 '47 S 1613, 1949, '50 '47); 209
    - Commenmorate 50th anniversey Spanish American War, 1948; H J RES 308
    - Exempt States from Conveyance Tax (H R 11170, 1961, '58 1958); 478
    - Foreign Policy Commission (H J RES 521, 1950, 1950); H J RES 525
    - Plants toconvert seawater to fresh (H R 6031 H R #650, 1949, '48 '50 '48 '49); 859
    - Hawaii Statehood thr. 49 (H R 1125, 1950, '46 '47); 866
    - Additional Funds Terminal Annex P.O. (H R 4647 H R 5780, 1949, '48 '49 '48); 1154
    - Pensions to Teamsters in Spanish American War (H R 4678, 1950, '51 '45); 1349
    - Automobile Credit Control, 1949; 1552
    - Army Retired Officers, 1949; 5037
    - unclear, H R 4913
  - RELIEF BILLS (same arrangement)
    - Newmann, 1949, '48; H R 700 (Box Box 5)
    - Khangani (H R 2284, 1951, '49 '49); 785
    - Cavanaugh (H R 3772, 1949, '51 '49); 786
    - Serlin (H R 4896, 1949, '47 '48 '48); 1059
    - Dortort H R 4334, 1949, '47 '48 '47); 1060
    - Green (private Law 21-H R 6483, 1949, '47 '47 1949, '46); 1061
    - Tebar thr. 51 (H R 4486 '51, H Congr., 1958, '47 62- '51); 1465
    - Flint (Private Law 440, 1949, '50 '50); 1871; 2 folders
    - Degerlund, 1949, '50; 1872
    - Robinson (H R 9371, 1951, '50 '52 '50); 2171
    - Little field, 1949 '50; 4331
    - Shiro Takomura (Private Law 584, 1950, '47 '48 '49 '50); 4371
    - Haves, 1949; 4907
    - Young Yuk Ho Kue, 1952; 6450
    - Serviarian, 1957, '56; 7119; (2 folders)
    - American Liquid Gas, 1949; 8435
    - Mow (H R 3805, 1950, '51 '50); 8452
    - Tam 2 folders (H R 5682 '55), 1957, '55 '48; 1569
  - File of RELIEF BILLS in folders, 1954-'56
    - Perjessy, 1951, '50; H. R. 777 (Box Box 6)
    - Meyers (H R 1181 82th Congress 1st Session 1951. H R9238 81st Congress 2nd Session, 1951, '50 '1950); 778
    - Hachisuka (H R 9787 81st Congress 2nd Session, 1951, '50 '50); 779
    - Tomkins, 1951, '50; 781
    - Oberdorfer (H R 7652 81st Congr. 2nd Session, (private Law 335 82nd Congr. 1st Session, 1951, '50 '51; 782
    - Abelis (private Law 165 82nd Congr. 1st Session, 1951, '50 '51); 783
    - Albano (H R 5400 81st Congr. 1st Session, 1951, '49 '53 '49); 787
    - Gee, John Y C, 1951; 789
    - Karszosiedlewski, 1951, '49 '50; 788
    - Kang Duk Yee (or Mrs. John J Hassett), 1953, '52; 845
    - Primitivo A. Cuenca, 1953, '52; 846
    - Sister Monica Grant (private law 318 82nd Congr. 1st Session), 1951; 1135
    - Wisiolowski (Private law 740 82nd Congr. 2nd Session, 1951, '52 '52); 1261
    - Dejczakowski, 1951; 1262
    - Tirbak (H R 6949 80st Congr. 2nd Session, 1951, '48 '48); 1466
    - Wong Ah May, 1951, '52; 5582
    - Musa Bajis Mahmud, 1952; 6066
    - Mohamed Kamel Muhyiddeen Mohamad, 1952; 6068
    - Viola N. Moore, 1953, '52; 7675
    - Toy Wong, Jan 1952; 7742
  - BILLS introduced by McDounough
    Arrangement as above
    - Sending Troops abroad, 1951; H J RES 91 (Box Box 6)
    - Foreign Policy Committee, 1951; 136
    - Congressional Authorizationsending troops abroad, 1951; 158
    - World Health Organization, 1952; 325
    - Naval Academy (H R. 115 80st Congress 1st Session, 1951, '45 '46 '47 '47; H J 1348
    - P O minimum spacerequirement, 1951, '48 '49; 1353
    - L A Post Office site ((H R 870 81st Congress 1st Session, n.d.) '49; 1355
    - L A Parcel Post site, 1952; 1356
    - Customs House site, 1951; 1357
    - L A Federal Office building site ((H R 867 81st Congr. 1st, n.d.) '49; 1358
    - L A Federal Office building construction (H R 3795 80st Congr. 1st Session, 1951, '47 '48 '49 '47; 1360
    - L A Parcel Post Bldg Construction ((H R 862 81st Congr. 1st Session, n.d.), '48 '51 '49; 1362
    - L A Post Office Garage Constr. ((H R 872 81st Congr. 1st Session, n.d.), '49; 1363
    - Postal Amployee Advancement Jap-Americans removed military areas W W 2, 1951, '50 '52; 1623
    - Marine Corps Representation on Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1951, '52; 2032
    - Increase in Civil Service retirement annuities (C S 995 82nd Congress 1st Session, 1952; 6438
    - Housing Act Amendment, 1952; 8218
    - Housing M D (H CON RES 222 82nd Congr. 2nd Sesion, 1952 '52); H CON RES 223
    - Amend Defense Production Act of 1950, '52 82 Congr. 2ns Session, H R 7079
  - BILLS introduced by Sen McDonough in Manilla folders 83 Congress, 1953
    Arranged by Bill nr. Horizontal: Subject, year(s) of introduction correspondance, related Bills
    - Maryland Tobacco price support, H R 1432 (Box Box 7)
    - Ext. Government reorganization Union Calender 7 H R 6, 1979
    - Limit Army Officers, 2332
    - 2nd Supplemental appropr., 3053
    - Ext. Agricultural Act, 1953; 3480
    - Hawaii Statehood, 3575
    - Tidelands H R 5134 H RES 193 232 House Report 215, 4198
    - Civil Service Leave, 4654
    - 1st Indian Offices appropriations, 4663
    - Interior appropriartions, 4828
    - Justice, State,Commerce appropr., 4974
    - Small Business Administration, 5141
    - Fedxral Unemployment Tax, 5173
    - Agriculture Appropr., 5227
    - Lobor etc Dept Appropr., 5246
    - Pakistan Wheat, 5659
    - 2nd Appopr. Indi Offices, 5690
    - Mutual Security Act, 1951; 5710
    - Amend Trade agreement Ext act, 5894
    - Defense Dept Appropr., 5969
    - Emergency Famine Relief, 6016
    - Supplementary Appropr., 6200
    - Mutual Security Appropr., 6391
    - Immigration, 6481
    - Trade Agreement Extension, 9495
    - F H A Insurance, H J RES 160
    - New Health etc. Dept., 179
    - Reorganisation plan 2, 236
    - Excess Profit Tax Extension, 326
    - Reorganisation plan 6, H J RES 264
  - BILLS introduced/sponsored by Sen McDonough 83 Congress, 1953/54
    - Airforce Academy H R 80, 1345 5337 5834 (proposed sites,i.a. Hemet), 1953,'49 '50 '51 '54; H R 329 (Box Box 8)
    - Claim of Zapp onferring juriseiction on US Distr. Court of Calif. to hear etc., HR 4910, 1951, '52; 853
    - Establish Marine Corps Secretary of Navy(ASS.) HR 5450, 1951,'49 '50; 1351
    - Improvement L A Long Beach Harbor, H R 3054 9859 Pub;ic Law 780, 1953,'54; 4086
    - New Dollar Bill Design H R 4727, 1953; 4884
    - Display use of flag of US, emendment of J R of H R 1752 2811 2744 3884 H RES 64 167, 56 S 555 Public Law 107, 829, June 22 1942, 1942, '51 '53; H J RES 56
    - Arr.aphabetical folders /eveveloppes